警察学校3
初为人师
20分钟后关门
We close in 20 minutes.
该死!
Damn!
谢谢
Thanks.
- 这两个该死的家伙在哪里? - 车库太大 老大
- Where the hell are these clowns? - It is a large garage, sir.
- 我们在这儿! - 你白痴呀?
- We're over here! - Are you an idiot?
他们在那儿
There they are.
蹲下
Get down.
人齐了
It's about time.
我闻够了尾气
I've sucked up enough fumesto last me a lifetime.
起来!
Stand up!
谁安排的 这么变态的约会?
What's with all this deep - throat crap?
别看我 是他的主意
Don't look at me. It wasn't my ideato meet here. It was his.
不能让人看见我们在一起
We shouldn't be seen together.
注意安全
Just thinking of the safety factorof Operation Fiasco.
我这么想的 先生
That's what I call this, sir.
一群白痴
I work with the village idiot.
- 你们有什么好主意? - 老大 你的眼镜
- Do you guys have any idea - - - Sir, your glasses!
你们… 摘掉眼镜!
Do you guys.... Take off your glasses.
你们认为本州 应该有几所警校?
Do you guys have any idea how manypolice academies are in this state?
- 是巧问妙答吗 老大? - 不 不是
- Is this a trick question, sir? - No, this is not a trick question, sir.
- 两所 - 错!
- Two. - Wrong.
据我所知 有一所警校要关门
My sources have informed me thatone of them is about to be terminated.
- 哪一个? - 不知道
- Which one? - I don't know.
还没有最后定
They haven't decided yet.
所以叫你们来
And that's where you two come in.
我需要两员干将 证实拉萨尔警校不如我的
I need two good men that'll make sureLassard's academy fails and not mine.
我需要两员干将 收集拉萨尔警校的信息…
I need two good menthat'll inform on Lassard's academy...
然后告诉我 他们的一切
and tell me every move they make.
我需要两员干将 能够卖母求荣
I need two good menthat'll sell out their mothers to get ahead.
- 那就是我们 - 很好
- That's us. - Good.
可以走了吗?
Can we go now?
我们分开走
We should split up.
注意安全 我们先走
Safety factor. We'll go first.
好像关门了 老大
Looks like it's closed, sir.
我们被锁在里面了
They locked us in.
车!
The car!
别担心 老大!
No problem, sir!
抓到了! 快停下!
I got it! Please!
- 我的车! - 快停下!
- My car! - Please, stop!
我的车
My car.
作为这个州的州长…
As governor of this great state of ours...
我自豪地看到 这些即将毕业的警官
it fills me with prideto see these graduating police cadets.
同时告诉大家 一个坏消息…
I'm also sad to tell you...
这是最后一次 有两个班毕业
that this is the last timewe will be graduating two classes.
什么?
What?
是紧缩开支的时候了一所警校 将被关闭
It's time to tighten our belts.It's time to close one of the academies.
但是 关闭哪一所呢? 为了公平起见…
But in the spirit of fair play, which isthe hallmark of my administration...
我指定了一个委员会…
I have appointed a committee...
来评估 比较两所警校
to evaluate and comparethe two academies.
这样 警校的命运 就握在他们自己手中
That way, their fate will restin their own hands.
我确信 两位校长 都会好好把握机会…
I am certain that both commandantswill welcome such a challenge.
打到了!
Got it!
是这样吗 毛瑟校长? 拉萨尔校长?
Isn't that true, Comdt. Mauserand Comdt. Lassard?
好吧 拉萨尔校长 祝您好运
Well, Comdt. Lassard, good luck, sir.
- 祝好学校获胜 - 应该是这样 先生
- May the better academy win. - We intend to, sir.
别太自信 毛瑟校长
Don't be too sure, Comdt. Mauser.
我们有很好的生源 很好的师资
We have many wonderful new recruitswhich we shall mold in my own image.
如您所愿 先生
Promise me you'll do that, sir, please.
先生 委员会
Sir, the committee.
女士们 先生们 荣幸地告诉大家
Ladies, gentlemen, truly a pleasure.
谁要骑警保护 不要羞于启齿
Anyone need a ride, police escort?Don't hesitate to ask.
州长 讲得好!
Governor, magnificent speech!
好啊! 为你鼓掌
Bravo! I applaud you.
为什么拐弯磨角 毛瑟?
Why beat around the bush, Mauser?
直接跪下 舔他的屁股
Just get down on your kneesand kiss his ass.
不要你来多嘴 卡拉汉
I don't need any tactical advicefrom you, Callahan.
州长!
Governor!
我知道您很忙 但我作了一些研究…
I know you're a busy man, sir,but I've been doing a study...
关于训练方法 也许您有兴趣
on some training techniquesI thought might interest you.
州长赶时间 毛瑟校长
The Governor is in a hurry,Comdt. Mauser.
写了一个备忘录
I could memo you on these, sir.
州长 我代表大家的意思
Governor, I speak for everyonewhen I say - -
我向您保证 州长…
Let me assure you, Governor...
毛瑟校长不代表这所学校
Comdt. Mauserdoes not speak for this academy.
州长 我想说的是…
Governor, what I meant to say was - -
克制一点儿 白痴 你让州长难堪了
Get a hold of yourself, you idiot.You're making the Governor sick!
你给州长留下了深刻印象
You certainly madea lasting impression on the Governor.
唯一的印象会是这份文件留下的!
The only impression that counts, sir,is in this file!
一切结束的时候 看谁会赢得学校
We'll see who's got an academywhen this is over.
学监!
Proctor!
- 不必担心 先生 - 对 让我们来解决
- You have nothing to worry about, sir. - Right. Just leave everything to us.
我们要让毛瑟自食其果走吧
We'll make Mauser eat those words.Let's go.
- 马浩尼 - 很好
- Mahoney. - Right.
好 继续 伙计们!
Okay, come on now. Guys!
噢 姑娘们 当然 抱歉好吧 继续 1号!
Girls, of course, I'm sorry.All right, keep it up! Number one!
运球 上篮! 动起来运球 上篮!
Take it on, drive it in here! Keep it alive.Take it in, drive in!
别松劲! 运球…
Keep your arms up! Take it! Take it on....
再来! 回传 停 停…
Try! Bring it back. Stop. Stop the playing!
把球给我 围过来 姑娘们我有话说
Give me the ball. Gather around, girls.I want to talk about something.
想想昨天…
I want you to remember from yesterday....
再围近点儿 好
Come a little closer. All right.
昨天 学了转身切入 今天 突破上篮
Remember from yesterday,you pick and roll? Now, ready and break!
2号 动起来
Number two. Keep it alive.
警察学校呼叫马霍尼中士
Police Academy to Sgt. Mahoney.Come in, please.
马霍尼中士办公室
Sgt. Mahoney's office.
让马霍尼来听 然后把你的脚从仪表板上拿下来!
Get me Mahoney,and get your feet off the dashboard!
很好 现在带球向前
Good, take it along now.
- 我很抱歉 中士 我不是故意的 - 没关系 这是我的荣幸
- I'm sorry, Sergeant. I didn't mean to. - That's okay. My pleasure.
马霍尼中士 我刚收到 拉萨尔校长需要帮助
Sgt. Mahoney, I just heard,Comdt. Lassard needs help.
拉萨尔有麻烦了?
Lassard's in trouble?
把它还给我!
Give it back!
等会我!
Wait. Wait for me!
噢 妈咪!
Go, Mom!
呼叫高塔中士
Sgt. Hightower, come in.
妈的!
Shit.
高塔 脱掉女裤 然后赶紧回答
Hightower, get rid of the pantyhoseand report to the academy immediately.
我马上来
I'm on my way.
尤金?
Eugene?
塔克贝利?
Tackleberry?
快出来 尤金 我放弃了
Come on out, Eugene. I give up.
你赢了
You out did yourself this time.
我真的找不到你了
Olly, olly, oxen free?
行了 塔克贝利 我已经不耐烦了
All right, come on, Tackleberry,I'm tired of this.
停止在后院犯傻吧
Quit fooling around in the backyard.
我是严肃的 我有事要告诉你
I'm serious. I got something to tell you.
快点 尤金 我真的忍受不住了
All right, come on, Eugene.I'm getting pretty tired of this.
拜托了 尤金 我有重要的事情要告诉你——
Come on, Eugene,I got an important message - -
真棒 塔克 你真的把我给耍了
Good one, Tack. Really fooled me.
马霍尼打电话了 他说拉萨尔得需要帮助
Mahoney called.He said Lassard needs help.
这一刻真是太激动人心了 我所有喜爱的毕业生都回来了
What a wonderful moment,my favorite graduates back.
学校正面临着一项重大的挑战
The academy is facingits greatest challenge.
多年来…
After many years...
毕业了许多优秀的警官 政府说…
of graduating many fine police officers,the State says...
它负担不起两所警察学校了
it can no longer affordtwo police academies.
上帝知道他们把钱都花哪去了
God knows what they didwith all the money.
我们的传统就是…
We have a tradition to uphold...
为荣誉而战!
a reputation to defend,and defend it, we will!
- 谢谢 马霍尼 - 随时为您效劳 长官
- Thank you, Mahoney. - Anytime, sir.
有新兵和你们的帮助 我相信我们能赢得胜利
With our new recruits and your help,I'm sure we can survive the competition.
赢家只有一个
There can only be one winner.
当然 输家也只有一个 它会被漂亮的赶出局
But also only one loser,which works out nicely.
我自然希望我们赢
I certainly hope we win.
然后我就能带着尊严退休了
Then I can retirewith the same sense of dignity...
这也是我一直以来带给学校的尊严
I have always brought to the academy.
解散
Dismissed.
给我滚开 小家伙 不然我就给你好看!
Get out of my way, buster,or I'll start playing rough.
- 别这么做 - 不 我就要这么做!
- Don't do that. - No, I will not!
你这样做太傻了! 把箱子给我放下!
You have the stupidest idea.Put down that suitcase.
- 你不能去警察学校! - 就要去!
- You are not going to that police academy. - Wrong!
你不认为这家里有一个警察已经够了吗?
Finally, don't you think one policemanin this family is enough?
住嘴 我才不管你说什么!
Stop it! I don't care what you say!
很好
Great.
好了 听着 我只是想跟你一起参军
Okay, listen. See, I just wantedto join the force to be with you.
我是说 我们可以一起开车 穿相配的制服 还能一起打枪…
I mean, we can ride together, we can wearmatching uniforms, share ammo...
所有的事情我们都可以密切协作
everything that makes a marriage work.
亲爱的 看 听我说 甜心儿
Honey, look. Listen to me, sweetheart.
- 警察工作是很危险的 - 我才不在乎!
- Police work, it's just so dangerous. - I don't care!
噢 不 不 别走!
Oh, no. No, you don't!
放开我 先生! 不然后果自负!
You let go of me, mister,or face the consequences!
- 早上好 法克勒夫妇 - 好 佩克特利夫人
- Good morning, Facklers. - Hello, Mrs. Pectelli.
在马路上吵架真是太丢人了
It is hell out there on those streets.
- 好吧 - 来吧
- All right. Okay. - Come on.
来 亲爱的
Sweetie, what? Come on.
我们都是成人了 我知道我们能协商解决这件事情
We're adults.I know we can talk this thing out.
没错 我知道你很聪明 解决这点小事没问题 只是…
Exactly. I know you're smart enoughto do that work. It's just that...
我是家里的顶梁柱 你呢 是我的老婆 你的位置就是在家里
I'm the breadwinner in this family, andyou're my lady, and your place is at home.
对吧? 来 亲我一下
Right? Come on, give me a kiss.
你干什…嘿!
What do you.... Come on.
你觉得我撞不倒这门吗? 开门 宝贝儿!
You think I can't break this down?Open it up, sweetie.
我是个警察 我是受过训练的 知道吗?
I'm a policeman. I'm trainedfor this kind of stuff, you know that?
够了 玩笑过火了 开门! 行了 你说过我们都是成人了!
All right, big joke. Open that door!Come on. You said we'd be adults.
那是我的…
That's my....
- 你想杀了我? - 我倒确实想了几遍
- Do you want to kill me? - I have thought about it a couple of times.
宝贝儿 马上给我停车! 我是严肃的!
Honey, stop it right now! I'm serious!
我不管 我要去警察学校!
I don't care.I wanna go to the police academy.
听我讲道理 啊? 现在听我说 你不会…
Listen to reason, will you? Listen to meright now. You are not gonna....
- 你要干嘛? - 我要把你从车上弄下去!
- What are you doing? - I want you off this car now!
我刚给这车打了蜡 你在给我找麻烦!
I just waxed this car.You'll get me into so much trouble.
这是条城市街道 不是拖车道 谢谢啦!
This is a city street,not a drag strip, thank you.
你要不喜欢 可以从我旁边超过去!
If you don't like it, you go around me!
根据纽约证券交易所此小时的报价…
...with volume on the New YorkStock Exchange as of this hour...
贸易达到56000000股 道琼丝指数上升4点 达到1507点
at 56 million shares in moderate trading,with the Dow Jones up 4 points at 1,507.
美元对外汇比价重新攀升…
The dollar is showing renewed strengthagainst foreign currency...
对英磅上升10%…
gaining 10% against the pound...
据联邦调查局有关利率下调的传闻
on rumors of the Fed'sdropping interest rates.
联合市场将受到极大影响
The uncertainty of interest ratesis affecting the bond market.
进行贸易需谨慎小心…
Trading has been cautiousand will remain....
这不是赛车场
This is not Le Mans!
搬运工 小红帽!
Porter. Redcap.
没错 就是你! 你能帮我一下吗?
That's right.Could you help me with these, please?
没错 来一下
That's right. Come on over here.
谢谢 这太好了 谢谢
Thank you. That'll be fine, thank you.
搬运工
Porter.
请…请坐下 拜托
Please, sit down. Please.
闭上你们的嘴 把你们的臭屁股放到凳子上给我好好地听着!
Zip your lips, slap your butts to the seatand listen hard!
这样好多了
That's a lot better.
让我成为第一个迎接你们的人欢迎你们来到这位于市中心的神话般的警察学校
Let me be the first to welcome youto the fabulous Midcity Police Academy.
你们将在这里度过生命中为期14天的冒险
We're about to beginan incredible 14 - week adventure in living.
我是你们的领导之一 凯瑞·马霍尼中士
I'm one of your hosts,Sgt. Carey Mahoney.
下车后 请排成两队
And as you exit the bus,please form a double line.
出发!
And march them!
谁干的?
Who did that?
嘿 伙计 这个地方够疯狂的 傻瓜们总使我跳舞
Say, man, this place is crazy. Suckersalways making me dance and stuff.
这是什么地方? 我觉得我不成
What kind of place is this?I don't look like I'm gonna make it.
你会做得好的 接着跳吧
You'll make it just fine. Keep dancing.
嗯 很高 好
Good, tall. Good.
嗯 很壮 不错
Good, strong.
对不起
Excuse me.
你是谁?
And who might you be?
我是山田乃木 利原田来的
Tomoko Nogata, of Tachikawa Nogatas.
"这是您漂亮的夫人吗? "
"And is this your lovely wife?"
- 学监 - 到 长官
- Proctor. - Yes, sir.
- 这个满洲人是怎么回事? - 满洲人
- What's the story here with Fu Manchu? - Fu Manchu.
我这没有满洲人
I don't have a Fu Manchu.
我是说这个外地来的小虾米!
I'm talking about the stir - fried shrimpfrom out of town!
他是Tachikawa公路巡逻队的…
He's with the Tachikawa Highway Patrol...
是国际交流项目的一部分 到这里学习我们的方法的
part of an international exchange program,here to study our methods.
我不是教我的学生们如何用炒菜的!
I'm not teaching my cadetshow to use a wok!
把他送到拉萨的学校去 他在那里更合适
You ship him off to Lassard's.He'll fit in perfectly over there.
他会有一个好寿司厨子
He could use a good sushi chef.
- 没意见吧? - 谢谢
- No offense? - Thank you.
亲我的什么?
Kiss my what?
对不起 先生
Excuse me, sir.
- 夫人! 我是位女士! - 噢 对不起
- Ma'am! I'm a ma'am! - I'm sorry.
这些枪让我很难分辨出来
Those guns make it difficult to tell.
您是教师吗? - 当然
- Are you an instructor? - Affirmative.
你是新兵吗?
Are you a new recruit?
- 是的 我… - 她当然是 但她非常非常害羞
- Yes, I - - - She certainly is. But she's terribly shy.
站直了 萨拉 别胡言乱语
Stand up straight, Sarah.And don't babble.
老师会怎么想?
What will the instructor think?
- 现在 听着… - 住嘴!
- Now, just pay attention - - - Stifle it!
别担心 萨拉 等我们结束的时候…
Don't worry, Sarah.When we're finished with you...
你会有钢铁一样的勇气 冰一样的肌肤…
you'll have nerves of steel,ice in your veins...
还有一对这么大的铜球
and a set of brass balls this big.
尤金 不要偏袒他
No favoritism here, Eugene.
巴德 他把事情搞糟了 来 狠狠打他一拳
Bud, here, he fouls up,you give him a good whack.
- 打中啦! - 这拳不错 够卑鄙
- Gotcha! - That was a good one. Pretty sneaky.
他是趁我不注意
Caught me off guard.
照顾好你自己 儿子 注意点尤金
You take care of yourself, son.And pay attention to Eugene.
我为你骄傲 你他妈肯定会成为一个好警察
I'm proud of you.You're gonna make one hell of a cop.
谢谢 爸爸 你能替我把这个给妈妈吗?
Thanks, Dad.Would you give this to Mom for me?
别忘了防守
Don't forget to buckle up.
这拳打得还真不错
That was a good one.
抱歉!
Sorry!
嘿 我爸爸跟我的关系好极了
Boy, my dad and I havea terrific relationship.
谁能把这玩意儿关上吗? 它快让我发疯了!
Does anybody know how to shutthis thing off? It's driving me nuts!
谢了
Thanks.
到了 700美元
Okay, that's $700.
- 还有小费 - 给你
- Plus tip. - Here you go.
嘿 等会 这是什么?
Wait a minute. What is this?
你给我的这是什么? 你在干什么 开玩笑吗?
What do you think you're giving me here?What, are you kidding?
我不要任何上面有金枪鱼的钱
I don't take any moneywith pictures of tuna fish on it.
快点 美国钱 你欠我700美元
Come on, American money.Let's go. $700, that's what you owe me.
喂 对不起 怎么回事?
Wait a minute. Excuse me.What's going on here?
- 不够 他欠我700美元 加上小费 - 700美元打回的?
- Not enough. He owes me $700, plus tip. - $700 for a cab ride?
- 你从哪打的的 横滨吗? - 横滨
- Where did you catch this cab, Yokohama? - Yokohama.
打扰一下 我是凯瑞·马霍尼军官 我能帮什么忙吗?
Excuse me. I'm Officer Carey Mahoney.May I be of some assistance?
- 是的 这个家伙想敲诈这个家伙 - "敲诈"
- Yes. This guy is trying to rip off this guy. - "Rip off."
- 可以看计价器 计价器不会撒谎 - 这是真的吗? 谁是你的理发师?
- Read the meter. The meter don't lie. - Is this true? And who's your barber?
嘿 狡猾的家伙 别以为你那蓝色的制服能吓着我
Look, wise guy,don't think a blue uniform scares me.
- 不 先生 这不是吓人的制服 - 嗯 不 这不是吓人的制服
- No, sir, this is not a scary uniform. - No, it's not a scary uniform.
- 高塔! - 那才是吓人的制服
- Hightower! - That's a scary uniform.
这家伙刚才说了你妈妈的坏话
This man just said somethingabout your mother.
他还跟这个家伙要700块钱的车费
He also charged this guy $700for a cab ride.
- 这是敲诈 - 计价器不会撒谎 你们可以看计价器
- A rip - off. - Meters don't lie. Read the meter.
他们不说谎 他们从不说谎
They don't lie. They never lie.
计价器不会说谎
Meters don't lie.
这个计价器说谎了 这是个说谎话的计价器
This meter lied. It's a lying meter.
- 价格公平 - 还有小费
- Fair price. - And tip.
- 你叫什么 小子? - Nogata
- What's your name, son? - Nogata.
- Nogata?新兵吗? - 是的
- Nogata? New recruit? - Yes.
- 那边去 - 好的 谢谢
- Right over there. - Thank you. Okay.
- 谢谢 高塔 - 别客气 宝贝儿
- Thanks, Hightower. - Okay, babe.
对不起
Excuse me.
刚才那肮脏的一幕肯定打扰你了 小姐…
That sordid little scenemust have been trying on you, Miss....
凯伦·亚当斯
Karen Adams.
你是凯伦·亚当斯? 不是开玩笑吧? 我们是舍友!
You're Karen Adams?You're kidding. We're roomies!
我会帮你住下 你脱下衣服…
I'll help you settle in.You'll take your clothes off...
- 我们洗澡 然后亲近 - 我很抱歉
- we'll shower, get close - - - I'm sorry.
我到这不是跟每个穿着蓝色制服看上去很可爱的家伙发展关系的
I'm not here to get hit on by every guywho looks cute in a blue uniform.
我只想成为一个女警察
I want to be a policewoman.
你会的!
You will be!
我们会在一起 一起谈天 我希望
We'll get together. We'll talk! I hope.
嘿 马霍尼 我看你的品味依然不错
Well, Mahoney,I see you still have very good taste.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 车不错!
Nice bike!
你把电池放哪了?
Where do you put the batteries?
给我让开!
Get out of my way!
一点也不疼!
That didn't hurt!
嗨 我开得很快吗?
Hi, was I going too fast?
我到哪去注册?
Where do I go to register?
- 我们走吧 - 科克兰 46号! - 好的 好的
- Let's go. Kirkland, 46! - Yeah, all right.
- 法克勒 你想往哪走? - 跟着他
- Fackler, where do you think you're going? - With him.
- 女生宿舍在楼下! - 妈的
- Women downstairs! - Damn!
快点! 快点 姑娘们!
Move it! Let's go. Come on now, girls!
- 赶快! - 好的 漂亮的将军
- Move it. - All right, Sweetchuck, let's go.
- 出什么事了? - 是他 他就是头野兽!
- What's your problem? - He's the problem. He's an animal.
习惯就好 他是你的舍友
Get used to it. He's your roommate.
- 舍友? - 泽得改过自新了 他现在站在我们这边
- Roommate? - Zed's reformed. He's on our side now.
是的 我曾经是个坏人 可现在我是个好公民
Yeah. I used to be a real jerk,but now I'm a people guy.
你醒了!
You're awake!
你喜欢什么音乐? salsa还是瑞格舞?
What kind of music do you like?You like salsa? You like reggae?
带着爱的节奏的?
Something with that love beat?
这首歌是我写的 选自我的第一张专辑 是这样唱的
This is a song I wrote, off my first album.And it goes something like this.
它原先是首情歌 我整理了一下
It was originally a love ballad,but I kind of spruced it up.
不 我不接受请求
No, I don't take requests.
好吧 小丑们…
All right, clowns...
我要你们管辖从这到操场的整个区域
I want you to police this entire areafrom here to the parade ground.
我要你们捡起每个烟屁股 每张纸片和每根杂草
I want you to pick up every cigarette butt,every scrap of paper, every weed.
我们会从窗户监督你们
Now, we're gonna be watchingfrom my window.
如果我看见手电停止移动 你们的麻烦就大了
So if I see these flashlights stop moving,you're both in big trouble.
大大的麻烦 好了 开始干活!
Big trouble. Now, get to work.
乍得 咱们走
Let's go, Chad.
- 泽得先生 - 不去学校!
- Mr. Zed. - No school.
- 你确信这有效吗? - 当然有效
- Are you sure this is gonna work? - Of course it's gonna work.
它真在工作
It's working.
一 二 三 四
Hup, two, three, four.
看 长官 我让所有的学员都很快的入门了
As you can see, sir,I have instant access over all my cadets...
所有的教师也是
and all of the instructors.
立正! 给我做20个俯卧撑 现在就做!
Attention! Give me 20 pushups, now!
什么也逃不过监视器的眼睛
There's no escaping the camera's eye, sir.
就象您看到的一样 长官 我能监视体育馆 教室…
As you could see,I can monitor the gym, the classrooms...
以及动画片
The Rocky & Bullwinkle Show?
嘿! 这是娜塔莎和鲍里斯…
Good! This is the episode where Natashaand Boris have Rocky - -
这是老片子了 我看过了 重新放
It's an old one, though. I've seen it. Rerun.
我们还有一些问题要解决 长官…
We have a few bugsto be worked out, sir...
但我相信您会告诉评估委员会…
but I'm sureyou'll tell the evaluation committee...
我们这里的工作是如何的出色…
about the wonderful work we're doing in - -
你在拿凉脸贴热屁股 毛瑟先生
You're chapping your lipson the wrong butt, Mr. Mauser.
我不会向评估委员会说什么的
I have no saywith the evaluation committee.
更何况 我希望两所学校都好
Besides, I want both academiesto look good.
噢 我也是 长官
So do I, sir.
什么时候评估委员会来?
And when may the committeebe coming by, sir?
这周剩下的几天委员会都会在拉萨尔的学校
The committee is spending the restof the week at Lassard's academy.
下周 他们会在城市管辖区内巡视
Next week, the Governor has themsnooping around the downtown precincts.
这会给你…
So that gives you...
几周的时间来完善你的拍马技术
a couple of weeksto perfect your ass - kissing.
时间很充足 长官
That's plenty of time, sir.
卡拉汉 你在这
Callahan, there you are.
关于这次评估我们得谈谈
We have to talk to youabout this evaluation thing.
我在我的…等你!
I'll see you at my....
四! 一 二 三!
And four! And one, and two, and three!
你们不仅要了解所有的交通法规…
Not only must you know all traffic laws...
还要掌握高速驾车
you must also master high - speed driving.
今天我们先从头开始
Now, we'll begin todaywith a leisurely spin around the course.
看着点 女士 你要往哪开!
Watch where you're going, lady!
好了 你现在可以点火了
Okay, you can start the car now.
但如果我听见任何刚才那些声音 你就完蛋了
But if I hear any of those things,you've failed.
钥匙错了 我马上就回来
Wrong key. I'll be right back.
不要紧
That's no problem.
战场上经常是这样…
Very often in the field...
狗是你们最好的朋友
the dog can be your best friend.
是你最忠实的伙伴
Your most faithful partner.
我喜欢狗 他们也喜欢我 嗨 宝贝儿
I love dogs, and they love me.Hi, boy.
首选…吐出来
First.... Out.
谢谢
Thanks.
主人与狗之间的关系非常重要
It is important to developthe master - dog relationship.
如果你表现出任何畏惧…
If you show any fear...
狗就不会尊重你
the dog will not respect you.
- 斯威特查克 - 我?
- Sweetchuck. - Me?
- 命令狗坐下 - 他们不听我的
- Order the dogs to sit. - They won't listen to me.
会听的 来 试一下
They will. Come on, try.
来 请坐
Go on, have a seat.
你应该让他们知道 谁才是老板
You've got to show them who's boss.
坐!
Sit!
这节课…
At this time...
我要向你们介绍…
I would like to introduce to all of you...
我的老师 他曾教会我如何打架
my instructor,the man who taught me how to fight.
请欢迎 如果你们乐意…
Please welcome, if you will...
约翰·赫尼中士
Sgt. John Hurney.
现在 我需要一位志愿者
Now, can I have a volunteer?
谁能上来吗? 嗯 很好 Nogata
Can I have a volunteer?Very good, Nogata.
我真不敢相信
I don't believe it.
噢 天!
Oh, boy!
他可真棒!
He's great!
你的打击技术不错
You have impressive moves for a cadet.
谢谢
Thank you.
您看 头脑确实比胸部更有力量
You see, it's a matter of the mindbeing mightier than the bosom.
有趣的理论
Interesting theory.
我想说"刀剑" 可是说成了"胸部"
I said bosom, not sword.
听起来不是什么大错误
Sounds like a common mistake.
不 我是说 这样太失礼 只是因为她太…
No. I mean no disrespect.It's just that she's so....
这女人真棒!
What a woman!
开始淋浴!
Hit the showers!
懂我的意思了吗?
See what I mean?
走吧!
Let's go!
男人小姐
Miss Macho.
好了 先生们 晚上10点了!
All right, men, it's 22:00.
该睡觉了
Time to hit the sack.
我们走吧
Let's go.
你死定了 条子!
You're dead meat, copper!
走吧!
Let's move it!
- 几点了? - 凌晨3点
- What time is it? - 3:00 in the morning.
好了 所有人 起床! 出发!
All right, everybody!Everybody up! Let's go!
到外面去!
Outside!
快点!
Let's go!
快点 你们这些泥桶! 我要是能保持这种速度 你们也能!
Come on, you sludge buckets.If I can keep up this pace, so can you.
快点 你们这些大蛆!
Let's go, maggots.
一个好警察总是时刻做好准备的一个好警察了解城市的每一条街道
A good cop is always prepared.A good cop knows the city streets.
- 赫奇斯你还好吗? - 他没事
- Are you gonna be all right, Hedges? - He'll be okay.
- 我能帮您什么忙吗? - 不用了 我们到了
- Can I help you with anything? - No, we're here now.
- 再见 赫奇斯 - 我得输液了
- Bye, Hedges. - I'll have to be fed intravenously.
先躺下吧
Just lie down.
这是什么? !
What is this?
我的床 从新德里弄来的
It's my bed. I pick up in New Delhi.
Posture - o - pedic 对后背很好
Posture - o - pedic. Very good for back.
喂?
Hello?
是谁?
Who is that?
想借我的香波使使吗?
Do you want to, like,borrow my shampoo?
站住! 说出你的编号!
Freeze! Identify yourself.
是我 斯威特查克
It's me, Mr. Sweetchuck.
我看你好像要逃跑 先生
You look like a manwho's going AWOL to me, mister.
是的 我烦透了有室友的生活那就是头野兽!
Yeah, I am. I'm tired of having a roommatethat's an animal!
我在家的时候要比现在快乐得多!
I was happier when I was at homegetting mugged!
看着我的眼睛 告诉你要放弃!
You look me in the eyeand tell me you're quitting!
别怕 我会照着你
Don't worry. I'll take care of you.
给我个机会…
You give me a chance...
我会把你变成一个真正的男人
and I'll make you into a man.
无论是否会把你折腾死
Even if it kills you.
感觉好点了吗? 我们走吧
Feel good? Let's go.
士兵们
Sergeant.
一招好的出腿…
A good kick may be all that stands...
往往将你的重要器官从…
between you and the excruciating pain...
142加仑的子弹碎片带来的极度痛苦中解救出来
of a.357 magnum slugshredding your vital organs.
法克勒! 上来!
Fackler! You're up.
柯克兰!
Kirkland!
泽得!
Zed!
- 斯威特查克! - 斯威特查克 那句话怎么说来着?
- Sweetchuck! - Sweetchuck, what's the word?
- 杀死他们! - 再说一遍
- Kill. - Let me hear it again.
- 杀死他们! - 好 冲!
- Kill. - Now go for it!
谁出的好主意在这儿见面?
Whose bright idea was it to meet here?
是我的好主意
It was my bright idea.
景色真棒 对吧 长官?
This is some beautiful view, isn't it, sir?
城市里闪烁的灯光 夜空中点点的繁星…
The twinkling lights of the city,stars in the heavens...
明月当头…
the moon in the sky.
还有睡眠精灵（Sandman） 从一个屋顶飞到另一个屋顶
And Mr. Sandman flyingfrom rooftop to rooftop.
啊? 在哪?
Where?
该死的 那是什么?
What the hell is that?
把这个狗东西给我! 事情怎么样?
Give me this damn thing.Well, how'd it go?
委员会当即觉得我们已无可救药
The committee knew right awaywe were hopeless.
很好
Good.
现在我要你们把警校学员们带到市区…
Now, I want you guysto take the cadets downtown...
去干些实地工作
for some fieldwork.
不成 学员必须在第十周后才能实习
We can't do that. Cadets don't gointo the field till after their tenth week.
- 他们还不具备那种能力 - 我当然知道 你个白痴
- They're not ready for anything like that. - I know that, you moron.
这就是整个计划下周 评估团就要到那里了
That's the whole idea. Next week, theevaluation committee is gonna be there.
- 噢 我明白了 长官 - 我可不信
- I get it, sir. - I doubt it.
对不起 长官
Sorry, sir.
那个时候我也会去 看着拉萨尔的宝贝儿们出丑
I'm gonna be therewhen Lassard's guys screw up.
你们俩人要保证让他们出丑 明白了吗?
You guys make sure they screw up. Get it?
- 是 长官! - 嗯 很好
- Yes, sir. - Good.
揍他!
Punch him!
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
打得好! 他看上去不成了 很好
That's great. He's looking tired. Good.
你的腿很有劲
Your legs are rubbery.
- 打死他! 对我说：打死他!
- Knock him out. Let me hear you say it. - Knock him out.
你干嘛呢?
What are you doing?
这可不是我教你的打架方法你应该象这样 象这样!
That's not the way I taught you to hit.You gotta hit like this. Like this!
现在 干掉他!
Now, hit him!
目击证人依然是定罪的重要根据
The eyewitness is stillthe main source of convictions.
米勒先生 我要你慢慢来 别着急仔细地看一下这些人
Mr. Miller, I want you to take your time.Study these men very carefully.
然后告诉我们里面有没有抢你店的人
Then tell us if you see the manwho robbed your store.
让我打消您的顾虑 米勒先生…
Let me reassure you, Mr. Miller...
我们这里黑 所以嫌疑犯是看不见您的
the suspects cannot see youwhen it's dark in here.
米勒先生? 他在这吗?
Well, Mr. Miller? Is he there?
您确定他们看不见我吗? 我太太说他们是能看见的
Are you sure they can't see me? My wifesaid they'd see me, and not to do this.
米勒先生 那边亮…
Mr. Miller, bright lights in there...
我们这边黑 他看不见我们的里面有他吗?
dark in here. He can't see us.Do you see him?
过早让学员们开始实习…
Bringing cadets into the field this early...
肯定是你的鬼主意
has all the makingsof one of your lousy ideas.
怎么了 马霍尼? 对学员们没信心吗?
What's the matter, Mahoney?No faith in the cadets?
很困难吗 米勒先生?里面有他吗?
How hard can it be, Miller?Is he there or isn't he?
我不知道他确实没拿走太多
I don't know.He really didn't steal that much.
住院倒是很宁静
The hospital stay was quite restful.
我希望我按我太太的话做了
I wish I'd listened to my wife.
看在上帝的份上 米勒 你能不能
For God's sake, Miller, will you take your balls out of your wife's purse...
把你的脑袋从娘们的怀里钻出来
and finger the dirtbag?
是他!
It's him!
- 我要杀了你! - 不 是他!
- I'll kill you! - No, it's him.
他是牧师
He's the one, the priest.
长官 说真的 我们没办法评估委员会就要来了
Sir, honestly, we had no ideathe evaluation committee would be here.
我们觉得这对训练有帮助
We thoughtit would help advance the training.
- 你说"我们"是什么意思? - 那是个令人作呕的阴谋!
- What do you mean, we? - It was a lousy idea.
现在我周围全是一帮新兵 还有那可恶的评估委员会!
Now I've got a bunch trainees hangingaround with this damn committee!
我一直喜欢 注意您 您是个极好的女士…
I've been, like, noticing you,and you're a nice enough lady...
但您太紧张了
but you're too tense.
您应该休息休息 放松一下 您应该平静下来
You got to relax. You got to calm down.
您对付太个的 小个的归我
You take the big guy,I'll take the little guy.
噢 一个警察
We got a cop.
别怕 我们以前是一伙的
No sweat. This is my old gang.
您想不想去抢个汉堡包然后看个电影什么的?
Would you like to go out to grab a burgerand then go to the movies or something?
伙伴们 我来给你们介绍 未来的泽得夫人!
I'd like to introduce you guysto the future Mrs. Zed!
嗨 小家伙!
Hey, son.
- 对不起 长官 - 什么事 夫人?
- Excuse me, Officer. - Yes, ma'am?
我们坐在非吸烟区…
We are sitting in the nonsmoking section...
可那个男的拒绝掐灭他的烟
and that man refuses to put out his cigar.
交给我吧 夫人
I'll take care of this, ma'am.
打扰一下 先生
Excuse me, sir.
您坐在禁烟区您能不能把您的雪茄熄掉?
You're sitting in a nonsmoking area.Would you please extinguish that cigar?
死去吧 我抽完了自会把它掐了
Drop dead. I'll put it out when I'm finished.
现在就请您把它掐了 先生!
You'll put it out now, mister!
撞他!
Hit it!
现在 抓住他!
Now, go get him!
- 快! - 我在努力! 我已经尽全力…
- Hurry up! - I'm trying. I'm going as fast - -
啊!
Drive!
这会对我们不利吗 先生?
Will this count against us, sir?
我在学校已经愉快地度过了很多年…
I've been here at the academymany wonderful years...
我很喜欢这里
and I'm very fond of it.
- 新兵们做的好吗? - 很好 长官
- The new cadets are doing well? - Yes, sir.
- 我们要赢了 是吗? - 是的 长官
- We are going to succeed now, aren't we? - Yes, sir.
很好
Good.
你要是再发怪声 琼斯 我就把你的嘴巴永远封上!
One more ping out of you, Jonesey,I'll tape your lips permanently together.
大家听着
Listen, everybody.
我让你们把今天忘掉你们还不用为实习做准备
I want you to forget today. You don't haveto be ready for the field yet.
- 我们会证明的 - 我们还没有输
- We sure proved that. - It wasn't a total loss.
当然没有
Of course it wasn't.
一辆警车 两辆市民的车 全部地 完全地…
One police car and two civilian carscompletely totaled...
三位市民投诉…
three citizens' complaints...
两位评估委员打着镇静剂
two members of the evaluation committeeunder heavy sedation.
我管这不叫"完全的失败" 你们呢? 不
I wouldn't call it a total loss,would you? No.
伙计 给我和我的同事来瓶香槟
Bartender, how about some champagnefor me and my associate?
来 我们庆祝一下
We're celebrating. Come on, Proctor.
- 我们离开这 - 不
- Let's just get out of here. - No.
嗨 这样喝很浪费香槟的
Boy, that's a waste of champagne, sir.
什么意思 马霍尼?
Now, what is that cracksupposed to mean, Mahoney?
意思就是 我们认为您分不出啤酒和香槟的区别
It means we don't think you can tell thedifference between beer and champagne.
你懂吗? 你们就是两个傻瓜
You know something?You two are brain dead.
打赌您分不出来 输的请客
Bet you can't. Loser pays.
- 我接受打赌 马霍尼 - 给我用同样的杯子来杯啤酒
- You're on, Mahoney. - Can I have a beer in the same glass?
- 介意我们蒙住您的眼睛吗 长官? - 为什么?
- Mind if we blindfold you, sir? - Why?
- 我们不想让您偷看 - 是的
- We wouldn't want you to peek. - Right.
- 看得见吗? - 看不见
- See anything? - No.
- 真的? - 真的 什么都看不见
- Sure? - No, I can't see.
好 转圈转圈转转转…好了 猜吧
Okay. Round and roundand guess the drink.
是香槟!
Champagne!
你赢了! 他总是赢!
You win! He always wins!
好吧 我们会付帐的我们从这儿走吧
All right, we'll pay up.Let's get out of here.
- 你两个怪人! - 您真的让他们长眼了 长官!
- You two jerks. - You really showed them, sir.
- 学监? - 什么事 长官?
- Proctor. - Yes, sir?
帮个忙 把这个给我摘了
Give me a hand with this. Take it off.
不 别慢腾腾的快点 这样不会疼
No, don't go slow.Go fast, so it doesn't hurt.
真疼! 我没事吧?
That hurt. Am I okay?
没事 这正好有面镜子 长官
It's nice. There's a mirror right here, sir.
我眉毛没了
I got no eyebrows.
- 我眉毛哪去了? - 这呢 长官
- Where are my eyebrows? - Right here, sir.
- 嗯 很好 很好 - 真的?
- This is going very well. - Yeah?
是的是的 非常棒! 马上就好了
Yeah. That's great. It's coming.
真棒 真帅! 您会喜欢的 长官
That's great. That's nice.You're gonna like that, sir.
让我看看
Let me see it.
看这 看那! 这的弯儿 每一处弯儿…
Look at that. Look at this,this angle over here, every angle.
- 我看不见! - 给您
- I can't see it! - It's yours.
你看怎么样 长官?
What do you think, sir?
我想我喜欢
I think I like it.
赫斯特委员非常生气
Commissioner Hurst was very upset.
他用了很多坏话来形容我们的学校
He used many bad wordsto describe our academy.
一些还是外语
Some were even foreign.
意大利语 可能还有爱尔兰语 我想
Italian or Irish, I think.
最棒的才会留下…
This is survival of the fittest...
经过在市区发生的这一切…
and after what happened downtown...
看起来我们不是最棒的
it seems we're not very fit.
- 长官 您不会放弃吧? - 当然不会
- Sir, you're not giving up, are you? - Of course not.
我从不怀疑我们的胜利
I have no doubt we shall be victorious.
噢 有一点点怀疑但 基本上 我是个乐天派
I have a little doubt,but, basically, I'm an optimist.
我知道 委员会会留心我们 在这…
Now, I know the committeewill be observing us here...
在战场上 在警察联欢会上…
and in the field,and at the Policepersons Ball...
因此 我们不能做任何有损于我们这身警服的事情
so we must do nothingto dishonor the uniform.
- 我刚才说什么了? - 解散!
- What was I saying? - Dismissed!
是的
Right.
这张图很清楚地标明了…
This map will pinpoint trouble spots...
十平方里以内的暴乱地区
over a 10 - square - mile area.
我们的负责区域有200里
This dispatch unit has a 200 - mile range...
并且数字化
and a computerized city grid.
这个数字城市网跟踪警车的活动
This computerized city gridtracks police vehicle movement.
- 清楚了吗? - 是 女士!
- Is that clear, everyone? - Yes, ma'am!
是 为什么不呢?
Yeah, why not?
进行催泪弹练习时 手册上说你们应该戴上防毒面具
In tear gas training, the manual saysyou should have your mask on.
在催泪弹从窗户投进来的30秒内出去
Be out of here 30 seconds afterthe canister comes through the window.
有什么问题吗?
Any questions?
好运
Good luck.
- 扔得真棒 高塔 - 进去了 不是吗?
- Nice throw, Hightower. - It went in, didn't it?
好了 所有人出来!
All right, everybody out!
所有人都出来了吗? 得分!
Everybody present and accounted for?
我感觉很好 我再在里面呆会
I feel good. I'll be in there if you need me.
听着 我知道你们这周过得很累…
Look, I know you peoplehave had a tough week...
但有些事你们应该明白
but there's something you should know.
你们也许会是学校招收的最后一个班
You may be the last classto attend this academy.
我不知道这对你们是否意味着什么但对我们是
I don't know if this means anything to you,but it sure does to us.
这就是为什么 我们不仅要你们继续努力…
That's why, we not onlywant you to keep up the good work...
而且要更加努力
we want you to work harder.
因为我们相信你们…
Because we think that you people...
会是这所学校有史以来最好的一批学员!
can be the best classthis academy has ever seen.
相信我 你们会成功的
You can do it. Believe me.
从前 甚至连我也是个差劲的学员
Once, even I was a screw - up.
让我们为了拉萨尔校长赢一回 行吗?
Let's go out there and win onefor Comdt. Lassard, okay?
Okay? 好 加油!
Okay? Yeah, come on.
立正!
Attention!
解散!
Dismissed.
你听见了吗?
Did you hear that?
没有? 当然没有我这么问你可真傻
No? Of course not. How silly of me to ask.
你离窗户太远了
You're too far from the window.
- 酷点 马霍尼 - 好的
- Look sharp, Mahoney. - Right.
- 马霍尼中士 - 嗨
- Sgt. Mahoney. - Yeah.
你说的话让我印象很深
I was really impressed by what you said.
你确实在意
You really care.
是的 别到处宣扬 这会毁了我的名声
Yeah. Just don't spread it around.It might ruin my rep.
我应该为我所做的一切向你道歉你只是尽力做出可爱的样子
I owe you an apology for the way I acted.You were just trying to be cute.
"做出" "做出"? 要是给我的可爱打分的话 满分10分我会得8分
Trying? On a cuteness scale of one to ten,I'm an eight.
- 5分 - 好的 5分
- Five. - You're right, I am a five.
听着 如果你接受我的道歉我也会接受你的
Listen, I'll accept your apologyif you accept mine.
- 一言为定 - 好的 你知道吗…
- Deal. - All right. You know something?
你有没有这样的感觉? 跟一个人接触10分钟…
Have you ever felt,after meeting someone for ten minutes...
- 你就觉得好象认识他两 三年了? - 没有
- you've known them for two, three years? - No.
- 谢谢 马霍尼 - 别客气 长官
- Thanks, Mahoney. - Welcome, sir.
对不起 打扰一下 当你的情绪好起来的时候我能回来吗?
Excuse, please. Shall I come backwhen all is well with your mind?
我的情绪好得很 不过你看上去有些紧张
My mind is as well as it gets,but you look a little tense.
你看 我很困惑…
You see, I have great confusions...
是关于卡拉汉中士
about Sgt. Callahan.
噢 你来对地方了 兄弟
You've come to the right place, brother.
拿起纸笔因为…
Grab yourself pad and pencil because...
爱情专家要上课了
the love doctor is about to speak.
在我的国家 书上是这样说的…
In my country, it is written...
只有美丽的女人的吻…
only kiss of beautiful woman...
才能比喻为玫瑰的花瓣…
can compare to petal of a rose...
宝贝儿
babe.
在美国 只说是没用的
In America, talk is cheap.
我爱美国!
I love America.
嘿! 还记得我吗?
Hi, there. Remember me?
记得 当然记得 我怎么会忘呢?
Yes, of course. How could I forget?
那是谁?
Who was that?
只是一位老朋友
Just an old friend.
我们为什么要庆祝? It's 毛瑟 42 拉萨尔 zip
Why are we celebrating?It's Mauser, 42. Lassard, zip.
你觉得我们做得好吗?
You think we're doing that well?
恶作剧怎么样? 别担心
How's tricks? Not to worry.
你的朋友忘了戴上她"提供出租"的招牌
Your friend forgot to wearher "for rent" sign.
她是个可爱的孩子 是我的有氧运动的教练
She's such a sweet kid.My aerobics instructor.
马霍尼 看见我的耳朵了吗? 它是一个废话的调谐检波器
Mahoney, see this ear?It's a finely tuned crap detector.
还是个可爱的耳朵如果我冲里面吹气 你会跟着到任何地方吗?
And a lovely ear it is. If I blow in it,will you follow me anywhere?
我真感到惊讶 你竟然还有勇气露面…
I'm surprisedyou had the nerve to show up...
你的学员使警察系统丢尽了脸
after your cadets humiliatedthe Police Department.
真让我恶心
Personally, it makes me sick.
你们说呢? 你们是不是也觉得…
How about you guys?Don't you guys think....
我来了 委员
Coming, Commissioner.
如果我叫他饭桶 你对我的印象会不会变差?
Will you think less of meif I call him a slime bucket?
事实上 我会请我的有氧教练去证实一下我马上就回来
In fact, I'll have my aerobics instructorconfirm it. I'll be right back.
- 嗯 过得怎么样? - 棒极了 我需要你帮个忙
- So, how you doing? - Terrific. I need one of your special favors.
在这?
Right here?
噢 我就喜欢用这种方式吃虾的男人
I just love a manthat eats shrimp that way.
- 你喜欢? - 是的
- You do? - Oh, yes.
跟我来
Come on.
- 他怎么做的? - 问题应该是：他为什么这么做?
- How does he do that? - The question is, why does he do that?
这是一种精神力量
It is a power of the mind.
敬你一杯
Allow me.
你这个笨蛋!
What kind of idiot klutz are you?
我们走 我的小饺子
Come on, dumpling.
我目睹了整个攻击事件请接受我的道歉 赫斯特夫人
I witnessed the entire attack, sir.My apologies, Mrs. Hurst.
请允许我告诉您 科普兰不是我的学员 他是拉萨尔的手下
May I say Copeland is not one of mycadets. He is a member of Lassard's staff.
你看上去不大一样了 毛瑟你变胖了?
You look different, Mauser.Are you putting on weight?
走吧 小饺子我们去洗一洗
Come on, dumpling.We'll get you cleaned up.
那是拉萨尔的人 先生! 把洗衣票据给我 我来付帐!
That's Lassard's staff, sir.Send me the cleaning bill on that, sir.
想要最后一只小虾吗?
You want the last shrimp?
- 我只想要一样东西 - 是什么? 我去叫客房服务
- There's only one thing that I want. - What? I'll call room service.
别傻了
Don't be silly.
我想让你等 在浴室里等…
What I want is for you to wait in there,in the bathroom...
我好准备准备
while I get ready.
- 为什么我不能在这儿等? - 我们刚刚认识
- Why can't I wait in here? - We just met.
好了 难道女孩就不能有一点点保守吗?
Come on, can't a girl bea little bit old - fashioned?
我一准备好就叫你
I'll call you just as soon as I'm ready.
嘿 这风有点大
Come on, it's kind of drafty.
我去找人帮忙
I'll get some help.
嘿 耐心点 我一会儿就出去
A little patience. I'll be out in a minute.
快点! 有人想用…
Hurry up. Somebody wants to use the....
快! 让我进去! 快点!
Come on, let me in! Hurry up!
你应该为你自己感到羞耻!
You should be ashamed of yourself.
我一分钟内就会把您的屋子收拾好
I'll make up your room in a minute.
你推着我的车要去哪?
Where you going with my cart?
- 我的车 - 让我用一下
- My cart. - Let me borrow it.
我是警察…
I'm a police officer - -
这是我的!
It's mine.
嗨 今晚太热了
Warm tonight.
你好吗?
How's it going?
…把车票交给他 然后司机说…
...hands him the ticket,and the driver said - -
真有趣 先生一个幽默大王 委员先生们
That's real funny, sir.Great joke teller, the Commissioner.
您觉得享受吗? 舒服吗?
Are you enjoying yourselves?Are you comfortable?
侍者 饮料都记到我的帐上!
Waiter, round of drinks. On me.
饮料是免费的 白痴
Drinks are free, you idiot.
噢 是的 先生瞧我多笨哪!
Yes, sir. How stupid of me.
如果您不介意我这样说 赫斯特夫人…
If you don't mindmy saying so, Mrs. Hurst...
果汁喷趣酒留下的印象非常迷人
that fruit punch stain dried real nicely.
你是干扰不了评估委员会的
You are not going to influencethis evaluation committee.
所以能不能请你擦干你的口水?
So will you please stop all this slobbering?
我想一切都会被控制住 如果我知道谁能胜出的话
I think I can get it under controlif I could only find out who's winning.
我只能这样说：拉萨尔的学员没给他们留下什么印象
Let's just say that Lassard's cadetshave not exactly impressed them.
非常感谢 先生
Thank you very much, sir.
管好你自己吧 先生
Get hold of yourself, man.
噢 上帝! 你崩溃了!
Good Lord! You're falling apart.
- 对不起 委员先生 - 你到底想做什么?
- Excuse me. Commissioner? - What the hell do you want?
我们接到报告说 一名裸体男子在旅馆里进行恐吓
We've had reports of a naked manterrorizing the hotel.
他很明显不在这张桌子旁边
He's obviously not at this table.
- 毛瑟! - 到 长官
- Mauser! - Yes, sir.
你能不能去管教一下这个裸男?
Would you take care of this naked person?
裸男? 是的 长官! 我会马上控制住他!
Naked person, yes, sir!I'll get right on top of him!
学监!
Proctor!
很高兴看到你这么开心尽管有个坏消息
Glad to see you enjoying yourselves, men,despite the bad news.
坏消息? 有坏消息吗?
Bad news? There's been bad news?
哦 给你的坏消息 我的是好消息
Well, bad news for you, good news for me.
你的学员又干了些他们惯做的好事…
Your cadets have been doingtheir usual fine job...
所以我似乎已经稳操胜券了
so it looks like I've got this one in the bag.
祝贺你! 当我认识的人取得胜利时我都很高兴
Congratulations! I'm so happywhen someone I know wins.
我一直认为这次比赛早已定局
I always think these contests are fixed.
等会儿
Wait a minute.
- 如果你赢了 那么… - 你输了
- If you're winning, then.... - You're losing.
抱歉打扰你们的雅兴了
Sorry to spoil your fun.
- 这不公平! - 有什么主意吗?
- It's not fair. - Any ideas?
我可以扭断毛瑟油亮的脑袋然后把它扔到大街上去
I could twist off Mauser's shiny headand roll it down the street.
打住 高塔
Hold that thought, Hightower.
快点! 该死!
Come on. Damn it!
长官 委员们…
Governor, Commissioner - -
女士们先生们…
Ladies and gentlemen...
请允许我向您介绍一位不同寻常的人 毛瑟指挥官
may I introduce you to a very special man,Comdt. Mauser.
正如你所知道的 委员会正在对我们两所学校进行评估…
As you know, the committee'sbeen evaluating both of our academies...
并且马上就要得出结果
and they're very close to a decision.
你们想知道他是对此如何评价的吗?
And you know what this mansaid about that?
事实是…
It's a fact....
"实时十哈马侯马"
It's a "facahamahoma."
这位先生说话很有艺术
Does this man have a way with words?
他说 不能把学员提前赶去实习并因此来判定一个学校…
He said you can't judge an academyby rushing its cadets out into the field...
或是根据谁的学员最诚实 不
or by seeing whose cadetsmarched the straightest, no.
你们知道这个被我乐于称作"警察先生"的人会怎么说吗?
Do you know what the man,I like to call "Mr. Policeman," said?
"忘掉学员们过去几周里犯的任何错误吧
"Forget any mistakes cadetshave made over the last few weeks.
"他们还在练习
"They were just learning.
"真正决定胜负的应该是这最后的几天"
"It's these last days of competitionthat should determine the winner."
毛瑟指挥官 我向您致敬
Comdt. Mauser, I salute you.
我们都向您致敬!
We all salute you!
今天是评估竞赛的最后一天…
This is the final dayof the evaluation competition...
尽管毛瑟的学校处于领先…
and though Comdt. Mauser's academyis in the lead...
胜负的决出还要看你们今天的表现
it's how you perform todaythat will determine our winner.
警界职员将关注着你们
Police personnelwill monitor your performance...
在犯罪场所的一举一动
at crime locations.
我的建议是 你们要认真对待
My advice is to treat thisexactly as if it were real.
立正!
Attention!
解散!
Dismissed!
我要去陪官员参加慈善赛舟会
I'm going to accompany the Governorto the charity regatta.
他希望你们两所学校各出一名学员作陪
He wants one cadetfrom each academy to go with us.
但竞赛怎么办 长官?
But the competition, sir.
委员们认为在一个社会环境里对学员进行评审是个好主意
The Governor thought it would be niceto evaluate cadets in a social situation.
学监 这是什么? 赫斯特说每个学校出一名学员
Proctor, what is this?Hurst said one from each academy.
他俩好得就象一个人一样 差不多
They're just as good as one man, almost.
电话吃了我两毛五分钱 但接线员不愿意把它还给我
The phone's got my quarterand the operator won't give it back to me.
交给我好了 夫人
I'll handle this, ma'am.
- 接线员 我是塔克贝利中士 - 那又怎么样?
- Operator, this is Sgt. Tackleberry. - So?
- 请放弃这位女士的2角5分硬币 - 我告诉过她我们会给她寄去退款
- Please relinquish this lady's quarter. - I told her we'll send her a refund.
- 你现在就还给她! - 对不起 先生 你能跟…
- You'll pay her now! - I'm sorry, sir, would you like to speak to - -
退后 夫人
Stand back, ma'am.
您能认出您的硬币吗?
Can you identify your quarter, ma'am?
胡克斯中士 我们从1区收到10 - 48记号
Sgt. Hooks, we got a 10 - 48 in Sector 1.
呼叫塔克贝利
Send in Tackleberry.
塔克贝利? 他在城区另一边高塔就在三个街区外
Tackleberry? He's across town.Hightower's only three blocks away.
呼叫塔克贝利
Send in Tackleberry.
听到他说的了吗? 照着做
You heard him. Do it.
- 斯威特查克! - 大厅真不错!
- Sweetchuck! - What a lobby.
占据电梯 楼梯交给我!
Secure the elevator. I'll take the stairs.
放松点
Easy.
胡克斯中士 10 - 48!
Sgt. Hooks, there's a 10 - 48!
很好 呼叫46号警车
All right. Send in car 46.
呼叫46号警车
Car 46.
高塔 高尔地区有伙流浪汉
Hightower, there's a roving gangin the Gower district.
噢 天 就是这
Oh, boy, this is it.
太棒了
Right, right.
向左拐…不 你们正驶向高速公路!
Take a left....No, you're going towards the expressway!
调头…
Take a U - turn on....
在弗林特大街调头…
Make a U - turn on Flint Street....
不 那是高速公路! 这是什么?
No, you're going towards the expressway!What is that?
不 等会儿 调头!
No, wait, make a U - turn!
- 我们去哪? - 尽管放轻松
- Where are we going? - Just relax.
什么也别说
Not a word.
…你在来回转! 停下! 别…
...then you go around. Stop! Don't....
我们正跟州长一起颁奖
We're with the Governor at the trophy.
举办这次赛舟会的目的 当然是…
The purpose of the regatta, of course...
希望为我的竞选再压上2万美元的赌注
is we're hoping to raise about $20,000for my campaign.
我想 - - -
I was going to - -
- 州长 好运! - 我们正向盛满趣酒的大酒杯前进
- Good luck, Governor. - We're moving toward the punch bowl.
喂 裁判员 选出胜利者!
Hello, Judge. Pick a winner.
我们停了下来
We've stopped.
- 你们能往后退点吗? - 我们向后退
- Would you back off? - We're backing off.
你们想干什么? 伤害他吗?
What are you trying to do, injure him?
毛瑟指挥官的学员从不擅自离岗 长官!
Comdt. Mauser's cadetsnever abandon their posts, sir!
跟某些学员不一样 长官!
Unlike some cadets I might mention, sir!
我的妈呀!
Holy cow!
马霍尼 随便谁 我需要帮助
Mahoney, somebody, I need help.
听着 餐馆工人们…
Listen, the busboys...
正拿枪指着我的鼻子
are shooting my nose.
你听见了吗? 那是真的吗?
Did you read that? Was that for real?
我们听见了 长官?
We heard it. Sir?
- 也许我们应该去看一看 - 那评估怎么办?
- Maybe we better check it out. - What about the evaluation?
我的一个孩子可能正遭遇麻烦 让评估见鬼去吧
One of my boys may be in trouble.Screw the evaluation.
我喜欢听你说脏话 长官
I love it when you talk dirty, sir.
马霍尼也许觉得他跟我们一样傻
Mahoney must thinkhe's as dumb as we are.
- 我们不会爱上那个废物的 - 没错
- We're not gonna fall for that stuff. - Yeah.
他肯定拼命想作弄我们
He must be getting desperate,trying to sucker us with that crap.
好 我们走
Come on, let's go.
把手举起来! 这是抢劫!
Get your hands in the air. It's a stickup!
如果有麻烦了 巴克斯特会通知我们
If there was trouble,Baxter would let us know.
抓住他们
Take them, boys.
你敢碰它
Don't you touch that.
不 别拿那个勇气勋章!
No, not the one for bravery.
那就是游艇俱乐部
There's the Yacht Club.
我们怎么过去 中士?
How are we gonna get there, Sergeant?
你包在紧身潜水衣里好看吗?
How do you look in a wet suit?
想活命就把钱跟珠宝都交出来!
Hand over your money and jewelsand nobody gets hurt!
你别想逃脱惩罚 我是州长!
You'll never get away with this.I'm the Governor.
州长? 你们听见了吗? 啊? 我们抓住州长了!
The Governor? Did you hear that, boys?We got the Governor.
你肯定会伤透你母亲的心
You must be breaking your mother's heart.
你怎么不去问她? 她就在那边
Why don't you ask her?She's right over there.
噢 她很象你
She looks like you.
伙计们集合! 我们的麻烦来了!
Gather our boys. We got trouble coming!
散开 散开!
Spread out.
呼叫不到巴克斯特
I can't get Baxter.
码头那好象出事了 就在那下个路口右转
Something's going on at the marina.Right over there. Take the next right.
放松点 你有权保持沉默
Just relax.You've got the right to remain silent.
- 你开过了! - 这不允许!
- You passed it. - They're not yielding.
- 向右转! - 不成啊!
- Pull over to the right. - Yield!
你又过了! 在那右转
You're missing it. There goes the right.
我们坐的是警车! 这不能右转!
We're in a police carand they're not yielding.
快走!
Move!
停下! 救命 马霍尼!
Stop. Hold it. Mahoney!
警察! 快停下!
Police officer. Stop right there!
凯伦 我去追州长!
Karen, I'm going after the Governor.
- 你还好吗? - 很好
- Are you okay? - Yes.
- 你穿着潜水衣真漂亮 - 你也是!
- You do look good in a wet suit. - So do you.
不许动!
Freeze!
把枪扔掉!
Drop it!
向前走! 让我的日子好过些…
Go ahead. Make my day...
废物!
punk!
不许动 警官!
Freeze, cop!
倒霉
Trouble.
[日语]万岁!
Banzai!
噢 我不是有意打你的!
I didn't mean to hit you.
我恨你
I hate you.
靠岸!
Pull over.
马霍尼 还好吧?
Mahoney, you all right?
好 接着追!
I'm okay. Just keep going.
给我让开 老东西
Get out of my way, old man.
嘿 马霍尼有麻烦了! 我们走!
Mahoney's in trouble. Let's go!
收到
You got it.
学监 你是个白痴!
Proctor, you're an idiot.
你生下来就是白痴你这辈子都是个白痴!
You were born an idiot,you'll always be an idiot.
潜水!
Dive.
快点 学监
Move it, Proctor.
我划这边 你划那边
I got this side,you paddle on the other side.
停下!
Hold it!
你还好吗 长官?
You okay, sir?
当心!
Look out.
咱们谈谈?
Let's talk.
- 还好吗? - 用帮忙吗?
- You okay? - You need help?
- 州长呢? 州长!
- Where's the Governor? - Governor!
别动 脓包!
Don't move, dirtbag!
一切都好! 我们再来一次?
All right! Can we go again?
我要感谢所有队员的帮助!
I'd like to thank all the membersof my racing team for their assistance.
我不会赢得这座奖杯 如果…
I couldn't have won....
…没有我众多杰出的警校讲师…
...without the help of mymany wonderful instructors...
和众多优秀学员的帮助
and my many fine cadets.
感谢所有的人…
Thanks to all...
这所学校将继续发扬它的传统!
this academywill carry on its fine tradition.